Finding Aid of the WUWM Records, 1950-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- WUWM Records, 1950-2014, UWM Archival Collection 2; 9.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes, including 227 audio reels and 161 audio cassettes) 398 digital audio files (96.2 GB)
  - 8. WUWM Milwaukee Ideas, 2002-2004
    - Career Development Center, with Tom Bachhuber and Tom Luljak, March 25, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040325)
    - Scholarship Campaign, with Lucia Petrie and Tom Luljak, April 15, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040415)
    - 2004 Milwaukee Elections, with Mordecai Lee and Tom Luljak, April 22, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040422)
    - Panthercom, with Bambi Riehl and Tom Luljak, April 29, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040429)
    - Alumni Association, with Barbara Flint, Joe Czarnezki, and Tom Luljak, May 13, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040513)
    - IDEAL, with Amy Batiste and Tom Luljak, May 20, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040520)
    - Black and Gold Committee, with Mary Roggeman and Tom Luljak, May 27, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040527)
    - Technology in Education, with Randy Ryder and Tom Luljak, June 17, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040617)
    - Center for Workforce Development, with Sammis White and Tom Luljak, June 24, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040624)
    - Center for International Education and Global Studies BA with Patrice Petro and Tom Luljak, June 30, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040701)
    - Low Income Taxpayer Clinic, with Christine Bauman and Tom Luljak, July 8, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040708)
    - Harvard Survey, North American Dialects, with Bert Vaux and Tom Luljak, July 15, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040715)
    - Dancemakers Concert Program, with Simone Ferro and Tom Luljak, July 22, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040722)
    - Institute of Aging and Environment, with Gerald Weisman and Tom Luljak, July 29, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040729)
    - Gay Rights Attitudes, with Paul Brewer and Tom Luljak, August 5, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040805)
    - Conflict Resolution Training, with Nancy Burrell and Tom Luljak, August 12, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040812)
    - Pharmaceuticals and Anxiety, with Cook and Tom Luljak, August 19, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040819)
    - Center for Economic Development, with Marc Levine and Tom Luljak, August 26, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040826)
    - Peck School of the Arts 2004 Season, with W. Robert Bucker and Tom Luljak, September 2, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040902)
    - Microbial Proteins Research, with M. Collins and Tom Luljak, September 9, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040909)
    - Milwaukee Planning and Design, with Bob Greenstreet and Tom Luljak, September 16, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040916)
    - Get Out the Vote, with Hable, Watson and Tom Luljak, September 23, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040923)
    - WUWM, with Ruane Hill, Dave Edwards, and Tom Luljak, September 30, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040930)
    - CABHR, with Allen Zweben, Laura Otto-Salaj, and Tom Luljak, October 7, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041007)
    - Fall 2004 Symphony Season, with Margarey Deutsch and Tom Luljak, October 14, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041014)
    - 2004 Elections, with Kathleen Dolan and Tom Luljak, October 21, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041021)
    - 2004-2005 Basketball Season, with Sandy Botham, Bruce Pearl, and Tom Luljak, November 4, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041104)
    - Aquaculture, with Rick Goetz and Tom Luljak, November 11, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041111)
    - Library Programs, with Ewa Barczyk and Tom Luljak, November 18, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041118)
    - History of Eating and Food, with Martha Carlin and Tom Luljak, November 25, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041125)
    - Health Care System, with Sally Lundeen and Tom Luljak, December 2, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041202)
    - Norris Health Center Programs, with Don Craig and Tom Luljak, December 9, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041209)
    - Women's Resource Center, with Merry Wiesner-Hanks and Tom Luljak, December 16, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041216)
    - Services to Students, with Mary Roggeman, Jim Hill, and Tom Luljak, December 30, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20041230)
  - 9. WUWM UWM Today, 2005-2012
    - Info Studies in the Age of Technology, with Tom Walker and Tom Luljak, January 6, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050106)
    - Edison Initiative, with Nigel Rothfels, Josh Zara, and Tom Luljak, January 13, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050113)
    - Invasion of Exotic Species into Great Lakes, with Art Brooks and Tom Luljak, January 20, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050120)
    - R2D2 Center, with R. Smith and Tom Luljak, January 27, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050127)
    - Kenilworth Update, with Mary Roggeman, W. Robert Bucker, and Tom Luljak, February 17, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050217)
    - Reading Circle, with Marianne Maris and Tom Luljak, February 24, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050224)
    - Human Performance Lab, with Ann Snyder and Tom Luljak, March 10, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050310)
    - BioTech Business Venture, with Sandra Millon, Mark Underwood, James Moyer, and Tom Luljak, March 17, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050317)
    - Environmental Writing and Reporting, with Dave Backes and Tom Luljak, March 24, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050324)
    - Alzheimer's, with Christine Kovac, March 31, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050331)
    - Center for Volunteerism, with Laurie Marks and Tom Luljak, April 14, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050414)
    - Small Business Development Center, with Lucy Holifield and Tom Luljak, April 21, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050421)
    - Marcus Prize for Architecture, with Bob Greenstreet and Tom Luljak, April 28, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050428)
    - GIS, with Bill Huxhold, Zong Peng and Tom Luljak, May 12, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050512)
    - Summer Arts Program, with W. Robert Bucker and Tom Luljak, May 19, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050519)
    - Teacher Education Initiative, with Alonso Thurman and Tom Luljak, May 26, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050526)
    - StoryCorps, with Dave Edwards and Tom Luljak, June 2, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050602)
    - Environmental Health, with David Petering and Tom Luljak, June 9, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050609)
    - New Provost, with Rita Cheng and Tom Luljak, June 16, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050616)
    - Copyright and Information Issues, with Tomas Lipinski and Tom Luljak, June 23, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050623)
    - Career Development Center, with Tom Bachhuber and Tom Luljak, July 21, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050721)
    - Center for Composite Materials, with Pradeep Rohatgi and Tom Luljak, July 28, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050728)
    - Volcanology, with Barry Cameron and Tom Luljak, August 11, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050811)
    - Toddlers and Security Blankets, with Richard Passman and Tom Luljak, August 25, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050825)
    - Wellness Works Program, with Cynthia Hasbrook and Tom Luljak, September 8, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050908)
    - Happy Retirement, with Keith Bender and Tom Luljak, September 15, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050915)
    - Weather Forecasting, with Paul Roebber and Tom Luljak, September 29, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20050929)
    - Access to Success, with Ruth Williams and Tom Luljak, October 13, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20051031)
    - Einstein@home Project, with Bruce Allen and Tom Luljak, October 20, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20051020)
    - Economic Growth in China, with Dennis Wei and Tom Luljak, October 27, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20051027)
    - Tourette's Syndrome, with Doug Woods and Tom Luljak, November 17, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20051117)
    - Alumni Association, with Andrea Simpson and Tom Luljak, December 8, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20051208)
    - Norris Health Center, with Julia Bonner and Tom Luljak, December 15, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20051215)
    - Peck School of the Arts Programs, with W. Robert Bucker and Tom Luljak, January 12, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060112)
    - Student Affairs, with Jim Hill and Tom Luljak, January 19, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060119)
    - Difficult Dialogues, with Greg Jay, Meredith Reitman, and Tom Luljak, January 26, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060126)
    - TRIO/Pre-College Programs, with Pam Clark and Tom Luljak, February 2, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060202)
    - Almost Home Documentary, with Brad Lichtenstein and Tom Luljak, February 9, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060209)
    - Drugs in the Water System, with Rebecca Klaper and Tom Luljak, February 16, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060216)
    - Creative Writing, with Maurice Kilwein-Guevara, Dave Clark, and Tom Luljak, February 23, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060223)
    - Peck School of the Arts Programs, with W. Robert Bucker and Tom Luljak, March 9, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060309)
    - Life Impact Program, with Rick Clark, Scott Gore, and Tom Luljak, March 16, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060316)
    - Substance Abuse, with Paul Dupont, Carol Haertlein-Sells, and Tom Luljak, March 23, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060323)
    - Soccer, with Jon Coleman and Tom Luljak, March 30, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060330)
    - Ojibwa Health Study, with John Dellinger and Tom Luljak, April 13, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060413)
    - English as a Second Language, with Nancy Barbieri and Tom Luljak, April 20, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060420)
    - Center for Volunteerism, with Laurie Marks and Tom Luljak, April 27, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060427)
    - Athlete Training, with Barbara Meyer and Tom Luljak, May 11, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060511)
    - Computer Safety, with Bruce Maas, Steve Brukbacher, and Tom Luljak, June 8, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060608)
    - College For Kids, with Cindy Ruffert and Tom Luljak, June 15, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060615)
    - Helen Bader School of Social Welfare, with Stan Stojkovic and Tom Luljak, June 22, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060622)
    - Center for Technology Innovation, with William Haseman and Tom Luljak, June 29, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060629)
    - Union Programming, with Scott Gore and Tom Luljak, July 13, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060713)
    - UWM Fundraising, with Lucia Petrie and Tom Luljak, July 20, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060720)
    - Volcanology, with Barry Cameron and Tom Luljak, July 27, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060727)
    - Teaching Excellence, with Diane Reddy, Florence Johnson, and Tom Luljak, August 17, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060817)
    - Light Therapy, with Janis Eells and Tom Luljak, August 24, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060824)
    - Teaching, with Stephen Percy and Tom Luljak, August 31, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060831)
    - Study of the Brain, with Fred Helmstetter and Tom Luljak, September 14, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060914)
    - Political Messages, with Paul Brewer and Tom Luljak, September 21, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060921)
    - Mandatory Res/MPS Employees, with Mark Schug and Tom Luljak, September 28, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20060928)
    - Lights On, with Pam Boulton, Rae Williams Dimilo, and Tom Luljak, October 12, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061012)
    - Renewable Resources, with Sarah Gong and Tom Luljak, October 19, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061019)
    - Special Education, with Dave Edyburn and Tom Luljak, October 26, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061026)
    - Arts at UWM, with W. Robert Bucker and Tom Luljak, November 9, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061109)
    - Climatology, with Mark Schwartz and Tom Luljak, November 16, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061116)
    - UWM Foundation, with David Gilbert, Brian Thompson, and Tom Luljak, November 30, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061130)
    - Architecture and UWM Campus, with Claude Schuttey and Tom Luljak, December 14, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061214)
    - WUWM, with Dave Edwards and Tom Luljak, December 21, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20061221)
    - Alumni Association, with Andrea Simpson, Lawrence Schnuck, and Tom Luljak, January 11, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070111)
    - TV and Sex, with Elana Levine and Tom Luljak, January 18, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070118)
    - UWM's Charter High School, with Nancy Frank, Kirk Harris, and Tom Luljak, January 25, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070125)
    - Wounded Soldiers, with Randy Lambrecht, Cynthia Hasbrook, and Tom Luljak, February 8, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070208)
    - Science Bag, with Andrew Petto and Tom Luljak, February 15, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070215)
    - StoryCorps, with Anne Basting, Joan Johnson, Mary Milinkovich, and Tom Luljak, February 22, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070222)
    - Career Development, with Tom Bachhuber, Cindy Petrites, and Tom Luljak, March 8, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070308)
    - Teaching Excellence, with John Kahl, Jenny Wanasek, and Tom Luljak, March 15, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070315)
    - Counseling and Psychology, with Azara Santiago-Rivera, Nadya Fouad, and Tom Luljak, March 22, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070322)
    - Norris Health Center, with Julia Bonner, Jane Ramsden, and Tom Luljak, March 29, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070329)
    - Institute of World Affairs, with Douglas Savage and Tom Luljak, April 12, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070412)
    - American Indian Student Services, with Diane Amour and Tom Luljak, April 19, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070419)
    - Campus Safety, with Pam Hodermann, Sherwood Wilson, and Tom Luljak, April 26, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070426)
    - Campus Safety, with Julia Bonner, Stu Tentoni, and Tom Luljak, May 3, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070503)
    - Honors College, with Robin Weigert, Larry Baldassaro, and Tom Luljak, May 10, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070510)
    - UWM's Map Collection, with Ewa Barczyk, Chris Baruth, and Tom Luljak, May 17, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070517)
    - Bacteria's Role, with Mark McBride and Tom Luljak, May 24, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070524)
    - Peck School of the Arts, with W. Robert Bucker and Tom Luljak, May 31, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070531)
    - Weather Forecasting Service, with Paul Roebber, Mike Westendorf, and Tom Luljak, June 14, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070614)
    - Freshwater Lakes Today, with Val Klump and Tom Luljak, June 21, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070621)
    - Baseball and Education at UWM, with Marianne Maris and Tom Luljak, July 12, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070712)
    - School of Public Health, with Rita Cheng and Tom Luljak, July 19, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070719)
    - Diversity, with Donna Shepard and Tom Luljak, July 26, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070726)
    - Breast Cancer, with Sandra Millon-Underwood and Tom Luljak, August 9, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070809)
    - Celtic Studies, with Bettina Arnold, Jeff Ksiazek, and Tom Luljak, August 16, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070816)
    - Center for Instructional and Professional Development, with Anthony Ciccone and Tom Luljak, August 23, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070823)
    - Peck School of the Arts, with Scott Emmons and Tom Luljak, August 30, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070830)
    - Great Lakes in Africa and US, with Harvey Bootsma and Tom Luljak, September 13, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070913)
    - Peaceful Negotiating Resolutions, with Rob Ricigliano and Tom Luljak, September 20, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070920)
    - Insurance and Literature, with Jason Puskar and Tom Luljak, September 27, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070927)
    - Carbon Dioxide, with Margaret Fraiser and Tom Luljak, October 11, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071011)
    - Excellence in Teaching, with Diane Reddy and Tom Luljak, October 18, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071018)
    - Blending Life and Learning, with Laura Pedrick, Bob Koleta, and Tom Luljak, October 25, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071025)
    - Burma, with Ingrid Jordt and Tom Luljak, November 15, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071115)
    - DocUWM, with Brad Lichtenstein, Terry Caddell, and Tom Luljak, November 22, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071122)
    - Black Men in Milwaukee, with David Pate and Tom Luljak, December 13, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071213)
    - Stuttering, with Carol Seery and Tom Luljak, December 20, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071220)
    - Study Abroad and International Education, with Jennifer Gruenewald and Tom Luljak, December 27, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20071227)
    - McNair Program, with Karen Dredge, Tomas Garrett, and Tom Luljak, January 10, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080110)
    - Addiction and Behavioral Research, with Susan Rose and Tom Luljak, January 17, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080117)
    - Center for Volunteerism, with Laurie Marks, Jonathan Marks, and Tom Luljak, January 24, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080124)
    - Africology, with Winston van Horne, Joyce Kirk, and Tom Luljak, January 31, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080131)
    - Wisconsin Politics, with Kathleen Dolan, Mordecai Lee, and Tom Luljak, February 14, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080214)
    - Adult and Returning Students, with Kim Folstein, Tomas Garrett, and Tom Luljak, February 21, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080221)
    - Gravitational Waves, with Patrick Brady, Alan Wiseman, and Tom Luljak, February 28, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080228)
    - Technology and the Disabled, with Dave Edyburn and Tom Luljak, March 13, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080313)
    - Science Bag, with Norm Lasca, Guilherme Indig, and Tom Luljak, March 20, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080320)
    - Research Initiatives, with Colin Scanes and Tom Luljak, March 27, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080327)
    - Community Nursing, with Jean Bell-Calvin, Beth Peterman, and Tom Luljak, April 10, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080410)
    - UWM Going Green, with Kate Nelson and Tom Luljak, April 17, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080417)
    - Green Roofs, with Scott Peak, Jim Wosley, and Tom Luljak, April 17, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080717)
    - Polls, with Nancy Mathiowetz and Tom Luljak, April 24, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080424)
    - History of Computers, with Tom Haigh and Tom Luljak, May 8, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080508)
    - Building a Solar Home, with Greg Thomson, Chris Cornelius, and Tom Luljak, May 15, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080515)
    - ZipCar, with Scott Peak, Larios Berlin, and Tom Luljak, May 22, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080522)
    - Summer Dance, with Ed Burgess and Tom Luljak, May 29, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080529)
    - Milwaukee Mosaic, with Joan Prince and Tom Luljak, June 12, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080612)
    - Electronic Bio-Sensors, with David Klemer and Tom Luljak, June 19, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080619)
    - School of Public Health, with Rita Cheng and Tom Luljak, June 26, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080626)
    - Campus Safety Report, with Stan Stojkovic and Tom Luljak, July 10, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080710)
    - First Year Center, with Ericca Pollack, Jessica Stein, and Tom Luljak, July 24, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080724)
    - Freshwater Industry, with Sam White and Tom Luljak, July 31, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080731)
    - Burma Aid, with Ingrid Jordt and Tom Luljak, August 14, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080814)
    - Career Development Center and Alumni Counseling, with Tom Bachhuber, Cindy Petrites, and Tom Luljak, August 21, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080821)
    - Community Media Project, with Portia Cobb and Tom Luljak, August 28, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080828)
    - Knowledge-Based Nursing, with Sally Lundeen, Norma Lang, and Tom Luljak, September 11, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080911)
    - Africa, with Jacques Du Plessis, Dick Kwooya, and Tom Luljak, September 18, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080918)
    - College of Engineering, with Mike Lovell and Tom Luljak, September 25, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080925)
    - Political Media Coverage, with Paul Brewer and Tom Luljak, October 9, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20081009)
    - SPARK Literacy, with Rob Longwell-Grice, Abby Kagan, and Tom Luljak, October 16, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20081016)
    - Peck School of the Arts, with Wade Hobgood and Tom Luljak, October 23, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20081023)
    - Job Security, with John Heywood and Tom Luljak, October 30, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20081030)
    - "Can We Afford College?", with Jane Hojan-Clark, Beth Weckmueller, and Tom Luljak, November 20, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20081120)
    - UWM Chair of City Development, with Bob Greenstreet and Tom Luljak, December 11, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20081211)
    - Black Male Unemployment, with Marc Levine and Tom Luljak, December 18, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20081218)
    - Postpartum, with Anita Doering and Tom Luljak, November 18, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 081811)
    - Sleep Apnea, with Beth Rodgers and Tom Luljak, October 26, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 080109)
    - New Orleans, with Cheryl Ajirotutu and Tom Luljak, January 8, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090108)
    - Emotional Intelligence, with Barbara Meyer and Tom Luljak, January 15, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090115)
    - Nerve Regeneration, with Ava Udvadia and Tom Luljak, January 22, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090122)
    - Research Foundation, with Brian Thompson and Tom Luljak, February 19, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090219)
    - Meditation, with James Topitzes and Tom Luljak, February 26, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090226)